aedas.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy & Cookie Policy | Aedas

**Your Privacy Matters to Us**

Aedas is committed to protecting your personal information by complying with requirements of Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486) and Europe’s General Data Protection Regulation. 

Use & Collection of Information

Generally, personal information we collect from you will only be used for direct marketing purposes by providing you with monthly updates on our services, promotional events or any other marketing material and information.  Such personal data may also be transferred to any other associated entities belonging to Aedas Group.  However, we may not use your personal information, including your name and contact details (i.e. email address) in direct marketing unless we have received your express consent.  If after providing us your consent you decide you no longer wish to receive direct marketing from us, please unsubscribe below or let us know by contacting us at the email or postal address listed below.

We intend to collect personal information from adults and do not knowingly collect or store personal information of children under 13 years old.  If you have reason(s) to believe that we have used , collected or processed information of children under 13 years old, please contact us via our email below.

Protection of your Personal Information

We will not transfer or disclose your personal information to any other person without your consent, apart from other associated entities of Aedas Group, professional advisors and third parties that provide services to us.  We will ensure that there are adequate safeguards in place to protect your personal information and that we are in compliance with our legal obligations.

Your Rights

You have various rights relating to your personal information.  Some of the rights you may exercise include:

  * Object to the processing of your personal information;
  * Request a copy of personal information in our records;
  * Update your personal information we have in our records;
  * Request your personal information to be deleted in our records;
  * Request for a restriction to how your personal information is used;
  * Withdraw consent to our processing of your personal information; and
  * File a complaint to the Privacy Commissioner for Personal Data, Hong Kong, if we fail to comply with your instruction or to address your complaint regarding the exercise of your rights.

To exercise any of your rights, or if you have any questions or complaints regarding the use of your personal information, please contact Aedas Limited via email, [privacy@aedas.com](mailto:privacy@aedas.com) or via our postal address, 31/F, One Island East, 18 Westlands Road, Quarry Bay, Hong Kong.  

 **Our Cookies Policy**

Aedas uses cookies to collect information about how you use our website e.g. which pages you visit, and if you experience errors.

These cookies do not collect any information that could identify you - all the information collected is anonymous and is only used to help us improve how our website works and understand what interests our visitors.

To collect this site usage information, Aedas uses Google Analytics tracking cookies.

This information is stored by Google and subject to their privacy policy, which can be viewed here:   
http://www.google.com/privacy.html

Aedas does NOT use cookies to gather information which could be used to advertise products or services to you on other websites.

Using our site indicates that you accept the use of these cookies.

Accepting these cookies is a condition of using the website, so if you prevent them we cannot guarantee how our site will perform for you.

If you have any queries, please contact us at [privacy@aedas.com](mailto:privacy@aedas.com).
